Recharge.
重新装载
(QUARKS HUMMING)
Complete destruction.
彻底毁灭
Maybe you'll believe in my robots now.
也许你现在相信我说的机器人了
I don't know about robots,
but something was attacking us,
我不知道机器人什么的, 但的确有谁在攻击我们
and with pretty sophisticated weapons, too.
而且有着相当尖端的武器
Well, whatever it was,
we'd better get out of here fast.
哦, 不管它是什么, 我们最好尽快离开这里
Let's try and move this door.
我们试试能否挪动这道门
Unnecessary destruction is wasteful.
Did you inspect it?
不必要地毁灭是种浪费．你检查过吗？
All relevant details have been recorded.
所有相关细节都已经记录下来了
See if there are any survivors
and bring them to me.
看看是否还有幸存者, 带他们来见我
Alive.
要活的
- Come on! Keep it... - Oh!
- 加油！撑住...  - 噢！
From your reaction
根据你们的反应
and your lack of knowledge
of the way of life on Dulkis,
以及你们对 Dulkis 星球的生活方式知之甚少
it would seem there is some truth in your story
看起来你的故事里面有些可信的地方
that you're from another planet.
你似乎的确来自另外一个星球
Of course there's some truth!
当然是可信的！
Look, it was your people who thought
we were friends of Cully's.
看, 是你们的人认为我们是 Cully 的朋友
The identity of my son's companions
can now be established,
我儿子这些同伴的身份现在可以确认了
though what has happened to them
is not quite clear.
不过他们身上发生了什么还不是特别清楚
But Cully has told you they were murdered.
但 Cully 告诉过你他们都被杀了
And I believe him!
并且我相信他！
(COUNCILLORS MURMURING) Why?
为什么？
Because I have seen these Dominators!
因为我见过这些统领者！
We were just taken aboard their spacecraft.
我们还被带上了他们的飞船
Believe me, they're callous, without pity!
相信我, 他们非常冷血, 毫无怜悯！
(COUNCILLORS MURMURING)
I would be grateful if you could tell me
what occurred on the island.
如果你能告诉我们那个岛上发生了什么, 我会很感激的
Oh, look here, we've told you!
哦, 看这儿, 我们告诉过你！
We're just wasting time talking
while Zoe's in danger!
我们在这里闲谈浪费时间, 而 Zoe 正处于危险之中！
Can't we get away?
我们不能逃走啊？
Oh, we wouldn't stand a chance.
These Quarks are deadly.
噢, 我们一点机会也没有．那些夸克很要命
- Any idea how they're powered?  - No. Why?
- 知道它们是用什么能量的吗？  - 不知道, 怎么？
Well, if we knew, we might be able
to put them out of action.
哦, 如果我们知道, 也许我们就可以让它们停止工作
Attack them? Are you out of your mind?
袭击它们？你疯了吗？
Well, they're only robots.
哼, 他们只是机器人而已
"Only"?
而已？
Do you really think we could destroy one?
你真的认为我们可以消灭一个？
It'd be easier if we had a gun of some...
如果我们有枪的话, 应该会容易一点...
- The laser gun!  - Eh?
- 激光枪！  - 嗯？
Cully, I think we stand a chance.
Cully, 我想我们有点机会了
TOBA: Take them to the others.
带他们去其他人那里
QUARK: Move.
走
I'll set them to work on the drilling site.
我会让他们在钻取点工作
Work potential and stamina
to be recorded and sent for analysis.
将工作潜力和耐力记录下来, 送去分析
Agreed. If any of them should escape...
同意．如果有任何人逃跑...
Then you will report the fact to me,
no personal action.
那你就将情况报告给我, 不要擅自行动
(SHOUTS) Toba!
Toba!﻿
Command accepted.
命令已接受
Hey, would you look down there?
嘿, 你看一下那下面?
That's the ruined building. Hello.
那是被毁的建筑．你好
What can you see?
你看到了什么？
- JAMIE: It's Zoe and Cully!
- We've got to get down there!
- 是 Zoe 和 Cully!  - 我们得去那下面！
Jamie, we'll split up
and get round the back of them.
Jamie, 我们得分开, 绕到他们后面去
- I'll cut across those cliffs.
- I'll go this way.
- 我从那些峭壁抄过去  - 我走这边
- Ready?  - Yes.
- 准备好了吗？  - 是的
Once you're inside, give me time to
get the two Quarks into your line of fire.
等你进去以后, 给我点时间让我把两个夸克弄到你的火力点上去
Here we go.
我们来了
(GRUNTS)
(EXCLAIMS)
This one collapsed.
这个崩溃了
Join the other specimens.
去跟其他标本呆一起吧
This is foolishness, Cully.
这很愚蠢, Cully
All clear.
安全
Best of luck.
运气非常好
What do you think you're doing?
Zoe's out there!
你知道自己在干什么吗？Zoe 在那边！
I know that, you fool,
I was aiming at those Quarks.
我知道, 你个蠢人．我瞄准的是那些夸克
QUARK: All specimens stand up!
所有标本都站起来！
TOBA: What are you doing?
你要做什么？
You were told to keep away from the Quarks.
都告诉过你要离那些夸克远点
Oh, but I do.
噢, 我是的啊
Whenever I see one, I go away.
我看见一个, 我就走开
But they're all over the island,
where can I go?
但它们在这个岛上到处都是, 我能走哪里去呢？
Stop! One of them is missing.
停下！他们中有一个不见了
The man Cully has escaped.
那个叫 Cully 的逃走了
Has he?
是吗？
It's no good, Jamie.
We daren't wait any longer.
这可不妙, Jamie, 我们不敢再等着了
Something must have happened to the Doctor.
博士那边肯定出状况了
I think you're right.
我觉得你说对了
- TOBA: Cully! - Down!
- Cully!  - 趴下！
I told you to stay away from the window.
我告诉过你要离窗户远点
- Do you think he saw me?
- TOBA: I know you're in there, Cully!
- 你觉得他看到我了吗？  - 我知道你在里面, Cully!
Give me that.
把那个给我
Now you'll see what happens when
the orders of a Dominator are disobeyed!
现在你将会看到, 不遵从统领者的命令将会怎样！
Quark, destroy!
夸克, 毁灭！
(WARBLING)
Right. Here goes.
好了, 开始了
(LASER GUN FIRING)
(WARBLING INCOHERENTLY)
Destroy! Destroy!
消灭！消灭！
(QUARKS WARBLING)
(EXPLOSIONS)
- Let's get out of here.
- CULLY: No! This way.
- 我们离开这里  - 不！这边
Stop.
停下
Task completed.
任务已完成